ROBBIE PARR

With over 7 years Python programming experience, React Native cross platform app development and 3D/VR Game development. Robbie is very motivated to learn new programming languages and frameworks, if he doesn't currently have a skill you want, he'll eagerly retrain and up-skill for you. In the past he has undertaken leadership roles and have encouraged team bonding, which improved team cohesion and performance at stress points in the project/group. After his studies finished, he created a community linking students and industry professionals in York, the Parr-ty Events, hosting several events, a multi talk event titled "Generative AI and the Future" being one of the highlights. He is looking for his first graduate role.

Education

University of York	BEng in Computer Science
Third year complete, results pending	2 nd Year Average 2:1 Classification

Key Technical Skills

- Strong Programming in Python, Java and Haskell
- Other Programming in C & C++, C#, HTML, CSS, SCSS and JavaScript, R
- App development using React and React Native (With TailwindCSS Styling, Expo Deployment)
- Continuous Integration and Project Management in Git (GitHub)
- Code Architecture in UML
- Databases using Firebase, Sanity and SQLite (Using SQL and XML)
- App Modelling in Balsamiq Wireframes
- Games design using Unity, 3D modelling using Blender
- File storage and forms using Google Drive (Docs, Slides, Sheets, Sites)

Key Transferable skills

- - -	Leadership Responsible Punctual Organised	- - -	Scientifically Adept, Especially in Physics Technologically Adept Diligence Dependable
-	Problem Solving	-	Discretion
-	Efficient	-	Perseverance
-	Hard-working	-	Resilience
-	Trustworthy	-	Resourceful
-	Adaptable	-	Reliable

Experience

Mathematically Adept

York Community Consulting	October 2022 - Current
Joined a technology focussed consultancy project as	Key takeaways
a Senior Consultant and upon completion of the	- How to build a client facing
project was promoted to a Software Developer in	ReactJS/Next.Js web application.
the wider YCC Technology team to continue	- Agile methodologies
developing the new YCC website. The website	- Working in a team of Junior
utilises React.JS/Next.Js, SCSS, JSX with a JavaScript	Software/Aspiring Full Stack Developers
backend and firebase data and API endpoints.	- GitHub

ROBBIE PARR

University of York, Baking Society		March 2021 - March 2022, Three
		University Terms
President of the Baking Society; leading a fully new small	Key	r takeaways
interdisciplinary committee team, organising the society	-	What it's like to be in a leadership
and the great events we put on, rejuvenating the buzz for		role
in-person events after lockdowns, working with notes from	-	Importance of good relationships
previous, uncontactable, committee members. I proudly		with society members and
hosted a multitude of events, being the face of the society.		members of small businesses.

The Edinburgh Woollen Mill		February 2020 - September 2020
Worked as a Sales	Key takeaways	
Assistant, helping with the selling of goods to customers. Ensuring an excellent customer experience.	 Customer Service An understanding of till GUI and the interface that is clear and concise, a "technical jargon" staff don't need 	abstracting away the low level

Shelton Development Service	es (Cranleigh) 31 July – 4 August 2017
One-week work experience writing	Key takeaway
software using Python, Pygame, HTML	- How to work effectively and efficiently as part of a tean
and CSS to re-create a licence system	- How to collaborate and ask for help in a team of
for the company's software products.	Software Developers